http://www.cruiseleaders.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase services from our company, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our company, services and other updates.
SECTION 2 – CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for service delivery, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us by contact form.
SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
SECTION 4 – HOSTING
Our website is hosted by a 3rd party hosting provider. They provide us with the online content management platform that allows us to market our products and services to you. Your data is stored on the hosting server via data storage databases. This information is stored on a secure server behind an active firewall.
Payment:
We do not store your credit card information on our website.
SECTION 5 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links
When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 6 – SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
All information that is submitted through this website is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all generally accepted safeguards and implement additional generally accepted industry standards as reqiored/
COOKIES
We use cookies to track usage patterns on the website and to offer other functionalities (such as geographic recognition, shopping cart sessions, etc.) You can turn off cookies, but that might negatively affect your online experience.
SECTION 7 – AGE OF CONSENT
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 8 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our website is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell services to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer by contact form.
Additional Terms & Conditions
Savings & Free Gratuities offer available on select ships and sail dates of 7 nights or longer.
Credit value varies by ship, sail date and cabin category.
Holidays In Motion reserves the right to determine promotion combinability per incentive
Offer applies to new individual bookings booked through Holidays in Motion, Inc. only.
Offer not combinable with other promotions or discounts.
Optional insurance is available and recommended.
Rates vary by date, are subject to space availability and are in U.S. dollars.
Certain sail dates including Holiday sailings and blackout dates may be excluded.
Offer good only for voyages of seven nights or longer based on double occupancy.
Some restrictions may apply.
Coupon has no cash value.
Offer is capacity controlled, cannot be combined with any other offer or discount and may be withdrawn at any time without prior notice.
Promotion applicable to permanent or dual residents of the U.S. or Canada.
Credit value may be a combination of prepaid gratuities and/or onboard spending credit.
Offer subject to change and is based on individual merchant’s terms and conditions.
Void where prohibited or restricted by law.
Offer valid only when you pay with your Visa card.
Any taxes are the sole responsibility of the purchaser.
×
